I'll allow you to so hot even when the
last time I broadcast live was somehow
it only lets me do it on my laptop um I
don't know exactly what to do because
none of my social media is in the right
State for what it is I want to do but
sharing it maybe there's someone out
there who will watch this and have their
own YouTube channel and have a thousand
subscribers at least and we can go live
on their I don't know between facebook
youtube and periscope as well as all the
paid systems what's the best for
streaming live with multiple people on I
want to have four people me included on
a channel so that we can have a real
discussion and continually do that and
as there's more than four people who
want to be part of a discussion branch
out more and more and more YouTube
channels or Facebook don't know
periscope doing that because this global
tech cooperative that I know is the
solution to so many issues because it
brings us together it makes information
usable it makes us more connected and
able to organize than any other time on
this planet but in order to be able to
actually get that done we need to be
able to have conversations and that's
where the World Cafe comes in a World
Cafe I was introduced to a few weeks ago
which is this concept of a group
discussion where people let's say you
add minimum of twelve people there can
be hundreds or even thousands of people
who get together in a physical space and
have conversations in groups of four to
five around generally round table and
they are given a question everyone on
every table generally has the same
question and they're talking for 20
minutes having a discussion bringing
themselves to that conversation and
that's all they have to do bring
yourself to the conversation contribute
when you feel called to and then after
20 minutes one person stays as the host
and everyone gets up and goes to a
different table to become seeds for that
conversation within the
group and the host stays to be the seed
at the original table and explain what
that table was talking about and then
people have a way to draw and write down
notes on a paper so that the people come
in can can see that and in this way
there's this amazing group intellect
that emerges of that it's not like five
people having a conversation it's like
the two hundred people have any
conversation and so I have the idea to
start hosting these in real life so that
we can start having the conversation
about creating it online and then in so
doing that and dealing with Minds I hear
around having a world
real world event and having to go in
into that space it is a strange
dichotomy because the actual impedance
pace being with all those people having
those conversations is actually my hell
like it's like way too loud way too
chaotic way too I can't think of that I
definitely it's harder to participate
I'm willing to do that if that's what
needs to be done because it'll be
monthly and it won't be ends maybe I
don't even have to participate the idea
of being able but the yet at the same
time that idea that idea of people
coming together and having a deep
conversation that actually leads to
action is my heaven and so finding the
way to breaking what is anxiety causing
and way to sensory for me into an online
space where where I can feel safe and I
can feel and be my brain works better
and and that's what we want to do anyway
and so in half the I wrote the blog post
this week and before I even published it
it became outdated because then I was on
periscope and one of the people were
like oh we can use this we can actually
use periscope for this medium the issue
is getting people onto periscope to do
it because periscope isn't none of them
are designed for this which is why we
need to meet on one of the ones that's
there that's free it's usable for this
format and create from those
conversations our social media platform
it's actually designed to have real deep
conversations in
group so our voices can be heard and
ideas can be generated and then in a
larger group of getting them what is
coming out of all of those conversations
together and how we create a platform
online to be able to facilitate that
whether it looks exactly like it does in
the real world where we have a something
we're drawing on and we're publishing
those those graphic representations of
our conversation whether they're
recorded and anyone can watch them or
whether some people don't feel
comfortable being recorded but right now
wanting to draw more and more people in
because the more people that are there
having that conversation the more
powerful the force that wants to take
action is as well as just that's
marketing like that's our equivalent of
marketing we want people to be able to
know that we are out there having a
conversation openly and honestly that
matter the conversations that matter
because so many people are overwhelmed
right now with what's going on in the
world and there's this division between
you know pros and cons and the left and
the right and the pro-life pro-choice
and black lives blue lives founder and
having these spaces of conflict instead
of like right but there's everyone still
to share their truth without necessarily
having a platform on right in your own
that just hey here is what where I'm
coming from and that's I believe how we
get to real a real space of connection
and not just surface level which is what
benefits capitalism right now is this
surface level overwhelmed overwhelmed
information overwhelm of going
right and wrong on the planet and like
how do you stay concentrated and how do
you understand all of this complex
information you don't one person can't
and we are going to design the system it
gives all of us access to that but in
order to do that we the people have to
decide what that looks like what we want
it to look like what what it looks like
so that we trust it so that it's
powerful can actually move forward and
so that all of those things are
conversations and so we're going to get
together either in the physical world
but in the meantime in the digital world
and
have conversations again and again and
again and if we're not taking action on
those conversations when when action
type things take place and nobody steps
up to take action why why aren't people
stepping up and then asking that
question like all we have to do is keep
asking people like what do you need what
should you be doing and why aren't you
doing it not here's what you should be
doing but like okay well I know I should
be eating better I know I should be
recycling more okay why aren't you
recycling more why aren't you eating
better oh because it's hard because you
don't believe in it because it whatever
it happens to be meeting people where
they are and giving them the tools that
they say they need because we all need
them even if you're someone who does eat
healthy listening to somebody who
doesn't eat healthy and the reasons why
because it's too expensive because I
don't have that knowledge because I
don't creating the technological tools
to help those people eat healthy also
helps the people who are it even healthy
even healthy it's like oh well here's an
easier cheaper way to eat healthy oh no
I really wanted the more expensive more
difficult way thank you I will stick
with it then great stick with it like we
can create something so powerful in this
world we just need to come together and
do it right now with me doing it all by
myself and not all by myself I've been
shown again and again that this universe
is here to support me but how like I'm
like how do I I don't know the hell I
don't know the how and I'm not supposed
to about mine it's okay to not know that
this just coming online and being like
okay I don't I don't know I know that
we're gonna get people online somewhere
to have the conversations and as people
are people to watch we're gonna have
more people joining the conversation
this isn't about having which is what
YouTube and Facebook and all they're
about having one person with millions of
followers we that's not over trying to
recreate we're trying to create an
actual dialogue which again isn't just
for people having a conversation with
millions of people watching it's for
people having a conversation maybe
there's dozens of people watching as
those DUHS and the people want to have
their voice heard and seen and want to
be part of a discussion they also get to
start a discussion and then how we bring
those groups
so that it isn't the same for people
having the conversation all the time
that it's rotating between them and
people have maybe there's one table our
table that is broadcast live and
everyone's having a conversation and all
the other ones are on appear in or zoom
having free for people conversations
that are that are powerful but they
don't want to be broadcast and then how
we coordinate people switching between
those tables and possibly having the
like that's where I want I want other
YouTube people I want people who because
I don't want I don't even know how to go
live with multiple people but I know
that on my on my iPad it's I'm not
allowed to go live because I'm not a
thousand subscribers I just still they
just want to recreate the hierarchy my
full we're not making body obvious and
we don't want which I get it's there for
profit system and which is why we're
going to use their for profit system
without paying anything until we can
make our not for profit system that we
all own together that's gonna facilitate
those real conversations and move us
powerfully forward and I'm just in a
state of like okay well how do we do
that how do we do that and both a little
overwhelmed about not knowing how to do
it and super excited that this is a
possibility that we are gonna have the
actual conversations and so if you
happen to be someone watching this
please please and you have a YouTube
channel with a thousand subscribers you
want to go live you want to have real
conversations not a debate not a you're
right and I'm wrong an actual
conversation about what works for you
and what doesn't work for you and how
you need the world to facilitate your
needs and how we together can work on
those solutions because we can when we
stop doing the debating thing and start
when I love a good debate but like when
we stop doing the debating thing and we
start actually finding what we have in
common and how we can support each other
those are the conversations I want to
have those are the conversations I want
to facilitate and the other ones are
going to happen two debates are gonna
happen divisions gonna happen it's not
about cutting that off and saying that's
not allowed but it's about is it
effective this is maybe not space let's
find a way to
move forward which is about having the
conversations how to actually do that hi
these like and subscribe